Privilege. Ambition. Desire. At Brideshead everything comes at a price.
Brideshead Revisited is a drama, romance film directed by Julian Jarrold.
Befriended by aristocrat Sebastian Flyte, Oxford student Charles Ryder finds that
the power and privilege experienced by the family is seductive.
On a visit to the ancestral home, Brideshead, he falls
in love with his friend's sister, Julia.
However, as his ties to the Flytes deepen, Ryder finds himself
at odds with their strong Roman Catholicism.
Charles Ryder, played by Matthew Goode.
Sebastian Flyte, played by Ben Whishaw.
Julia Flyte, played by Hayley Atwell.
Lady Marchmain, played by Emma Thompson.
Lord Marchmain, played by Michael Gambon.
Mr. Ryder, played by Patrick Malahide.
Brideshead Revisited is a 2008 British drama film directed by Julian Jarrold.
The screenplay by Jeremy Brock and Andrew Davies is based on the 1945 novel of the same name by Evelyn
Waugh, which previously had been adapted in 1981 as the television serial Brideshead Revisited.
The film explores themes of new love, sibling relationship,
based on novel or book, venice, italy, england.
The tone is emotional and thought_provoking.